# **Keren Reshef**

투 Rishon LeZion, Israel 🕿 050 9466446 🖂 kerenres7@gmail.com

#### **Software Developer**

Problem-solver and quick learner capable of understanding and working with complex systems and architectures from the top abstract level down to the actual implementation.

Experienced in a variety of programming languages including Python, Java, JavaScript, HTML, C.

#### **TECHNICAL PROFILE**

Python

Java

Linux

Django

Docker

CI/CD

C

**AWS** 

**JavaScript** 

React

SQL / NoSQL

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### Software Developer - Kyndryl 2022-present

Work with developers and architects in Israel and worldwide to build leading infrastructure management solutions focused on self-service management of dedicated private and distributed clouds. Designing and creating backend services using Amazon Web Services: Compute Services(EC2, Lambda, ECS), Storage Services(S3), Database Services(DynamoDB), Security Services(IAM, Secrets Manager), Management and Monitoring(CloudWatch), Developer Tools(CodeCommit, Cloud9, CodeBuild).

**Mechanical Engineer – Intratech Medical 2020-2022** 

Mechanical Engineer – Xenom 2018-2020

## **EDUCATION & PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT**

Infinity Labs, eight months bootcamp intended for training academics for software development professions | 2022.

BSc, Mechanical Engineering, Afeka Tel Aviv Academic College of Engineering | 2016-2019.

Military service:

2008 - 2015: Officer (captain) at the Military Police.

Main positions: company commander at a military prison, company commander

of soldiers at boarding crossing.

Job description: high managing skills, training and guidance of soldiers and staff,

working under high pressure, multitasking etc.